Email: lilycliu@outlook.com

Address: New Malden, London

Phone: 07308686787

Personal Profile

Junior Web Developer holding Master's Degree in Art Museum & Gallery Studies. I learnt front-end skills from bootcamp and self-teaching. The beginning of this year I developed an interest of coding, enjoy building websites, specialise in React, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Sass, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I also enjoy doing database like MongoDB, I have many years working experience in Administration, Sales, Customer Service and PA roles. I have excellent communication and teamwork skills, which I can bring to the team, I am a highly motivated individual, with an ability to work well under pressure in meeting deadlines and in fast paced environments.

Computer Skills

HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, Typescript, React, MongoDB, Git, Next.js, Microsoft Office, ERP.

Portfolio: https://64971f3e0342ec7a046dc57d--timely-jalebi-6c2a82.netlify.app/

Github: https://github.com/LilycLiu

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lily-liu-323568b2/

Skills

- Good attention to detail, organisation skills and customer service.
- Ability to work independently, efficiently and as part of a team.
- Have an enthusiastic and friendly approach, with excellent communication skills.
- Enthusiasm for helping and serving others, as well as developing myself.
- Native Mandarin speaker, fluent in English.
- Ability to produce consistently accurate work, even whilst under pressure.
- Ability to multitask and manage conflicting demands.

Education & Qualifications

Openclassroom, UK July 2023 – Oct 2023

• Web development online bootcamp

University of Leicester, UK Oct 2011 – Sept 2012

• MA Art Museum & Gallery Studies

National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan Sept 2004 – June 2008

Bachelor Degree in Art Humanities and Social Science

Work Experience

FACT https://www.fact-uk.org.uk/

Due Diligence Researcher/Data Processor at a research company in London. *May* 2020 – *May* 2023 Duties included:

• To conduct open source research and collection of intended subject matter according to

business needs: political, security, socio-economic, and terrorism issues

Process visa/citizenship applications and to consolidate foreign language information into
 English, and produce clear and concise written research reports

Jan De Nul Group https://www.jandenul.com/en

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Office Manager at a construction & renewable energy company in Taiwan.

Duties included:

- Assist the director with the management of his workload; prioritising accordingly.
- Filing, Scanning, Photocopying, Organising the meeting room calendar and Set up.
- International and national travel arrangement, Orgnising company events.
- Ordering office supplies, Contacting suppliers and Processing PO/Invoice.
- Supporting cash expense, HR hiring process and Dealing with shipping documents.

Bahamas Maritime Authority https://www.bahamasmaritime.com/ Apr 2015 – Nov 2018 Administrative Assistant at the Bahamas government organization in London.

Duties included:

- Answering incoming calls and emails via customers.
- Account manager for multiple clients.
- Issuing seaman's books and endorsements for seafarers.

July 2014 – Mar 2015

Sales Administrator at an e-commerce furniture company in London.

Duties included:

- Providing excellent customer support in a timely manner and Sales order processing.
- Stock control and Creating sales documents chasing up vendors.
- Administration of key customer accounts and supporting HR duties.
- Maintaining pricing information on ERP system and annual distribution of sales prices.
- Keeping up to date with all new process that require sales support input.

Egistec Inc Feb 2013 – June 2014

Logistics and Purchasing Administrator/Customer Service at a technology company in Taiwan.

Duties included:

- Stock control and Handling shipping documents and forwarder arrangement.
- Issuing Purchase Orders with relevant information (supplier, factory, sales)
- Engaging & replying to customer correspondence (emails, and phone calls).
- Preparing invoice and payment requests with correct sign off to Finance.

Extracurricular Activities & Hobbies

• Working holiday - Aug 2009~Feb 2010, I travelled across New Zealand.

References

References will be made available upon request.